{
    "subject": "resource/Eddie_Peng",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Taiwan",
    "human_readable": "Eddie Peng was born in Taiwan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9784247875213623,
            "question": "Is Taiwan the location of Eddie Peng's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.945280909538269,
            "question": "Is Eddie Peng from Taiwan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8536593914031982,
            "question": "Where was Eddie Peng born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6613115072250366,
            "question": "What is Eddie Peng's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6017333269119263,
            "question": "What nationality is Eddie Peng?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4841352701187134,
            "question": "Where was Eddie Peng raised?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4407479763031006,
            "question": "What is the origin of Eddie Peng?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4270326793193817,
            "question": "To which country does Eddie Peng belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41814470291137695,
            "question": "In which country did Eddie Peng come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2954842746257782,
            "question": "Where did Eddie Peng's early life take place?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eddie Peng was born in Taiwan.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8464_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which country did Eddie Peng come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8464_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which country does Eddie Peng belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8464_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the origin of Eddie Peng?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8464_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8464_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8464_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8464_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8464_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8464_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8464_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8464_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8464_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8464_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8464_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can confirm that the statement \"Eddie Peng was born in Taiwan\" is supported by multiple documents.\n\nHere is the structured JSON format response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support the statement that Eddie Peng was born in Taiwan. Multiple sources indicate he was born in Penghu, which is part of Taiwan."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}